clearxchange.com 2012-03-03

# clearXchange | P2P Payments for Financial Institutions | Privacy

This Privacy Policy only applies to the information collected on the website located at www.clearxchange.com ("Website"). By visiting the Website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, you are not permitted to use the Website. Please also make sure you read our Terms of Use to understand the additional terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Website. 

The terms "you" and "your," as used in this Privacy Policy, refer to each individual and entity accessing this Website for any reason. The terms "we" and "CXC" both mean clearXchange, LLC.

**Overall privacy statement**

We gather certain types of information about our users, so we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and with whom the information may be shared, and how to correct or change it. The Website contains links to other sites, and those sites might have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Policy.

**1\. What information does CXC collect, and what does CXC do with it?**

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our Website. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our Website, but certain features may not be available to you if you disable or delete cookies created during your visits. You may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser. CXC also automatically receives and records information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested. We may use tracking technologies for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to:

  * keeping count of return visits to our Website;
  * accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate, statistical information regarding our Website and usage of the Website for CXC’s own use and summary distribution to third parties;
  * determining which pages you use most;
  * providing content targeted to your interests and usage of our Website;

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. In many cases, your submission will include personally identifiable information. We may use this personally identifiable information for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to:

  * contacting you about a question or feedback that you have submitted through the Website;
  * contacting you about potential business opportunities if you have expressed an interest in such opportunities;
  * contacting you regarding sales and marketing activities; and
  * communicating with you regarding changes or enhancements to our policies and services or issues regarding your account.

**2\. Will CXC share my information?**

CXC will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-party advertiser or marketing organization without first receiving your consent, unless (a) we are working with other companies to provide you with information or services that you have requested, (b) CXC reasonably believes that your personally identifiable information should be shared to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process, or (c) your actions violate the law, our Website’s Terms of Use, or threaten the rights or safety of CXC or any person. If you use the services of one of CXC’s affiliates, you grant us permission to send your personally identifiable information to that affiliate. Our affiliates’ use of such information is governed by their respective privacy policies. Additionally, we may share non-personally identifiable information with anyone for any legal purpose, including but not limited to sharing it with advertisers, investors, and in the course of making presentations. If CXC is acquired by or merged with another company, CXC may transfer personally identifiable information about you to the acquiring company. 

**3\. What are my options?**

Users that need to change their information with CXC, or users that do not want to receive updates and information about new CXC services, may contact us with the request by sending an email to [privacy @clearXchange.com](mailto:privacy@clearXchange.com). Additionally, users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our online forms may contact us via telephone with their question or comment. If you have a question about the opt-out process that is not answered in this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to [privacy @clearXchange.com](mailto:privacy@clearXchange.com). 

**4\. What security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information in CXC’s control?**

CXC uses commercially reasonable security measures to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your user data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse, or alteration to data will not occur, we take commercially reasonable precautions to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Indeed, as you probably know, despite our use of industry standard security technologies, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. As a result, while we will use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

**5\. How will I know if the Privacy Policy changes?**

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first in this notice of our Privacy Policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our Website that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy statement. If we are going to be using the information collected from users in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we may notify affected users of the change via e-mail. Please note that, at all times, you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us your current email address. If the last email address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the email containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. Changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us.

**Questions, comments**

Questions regarding this privacy statement, or regarding any other aspects of the Website, should be sent via e-mail to [privacy @clearXchange.com](mailto:privacy@clearXchange.com). 

##  About clearXchange

Find out how it works and how your financial institution can benefit from clearXchange. 

##  Join Us

Get in touch to learn how your financial institution can join the clearXchange network.
